Good evening, I'm Kiho Onuma, Rina Machida and Edana Mori from Sakurazaka46!
Sakurazaka46's Youtube channel is now open!
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
It looks like we can do all kinds of things we want to do.
Aren't you excited? I don't know...
I'm so excited!
I want to say so many things!
To celebrate the opening of YouTube, we will be broadcasting live on May 4!
Yay!
A live broadcast!
I hope you are looking forward to it as well. Thank you very much.
And you are working on something, right?
Oh, that's right.
To commemorate this line,
I am making a mask.
I've been allowed to make masks,
It's fun.
I think it will be played after this video,
You feel like you're making it now?
Right now, in between gigs.
In between shows.
We're working on it right now during the tour.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Is it pretty much done?
Yes, it is.
It's just starting to come down.
It's coming down.
I'm about to start on the illustrations.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
There's the cutest little guy.
Come here.
Come here. Where do you think I should go?
I don't know.
Is this it?
Yes, this is it.
Miya and Shizuki are here.
Hey! They are cute kids.
I want to try something like this.
I want to have a big-eating contest.
That's good! You said you can eat.
I wonder who can.
I'm certainly curious.
I've had ramen.
That's good!
I've seen it!
We have a lot to look forward to, so I hope you will subscribe to our channel,
We will also have a live broadcast on May 4, so please subscribe to our channel so you don't miss it.
Please subscribe to our channel so you don't miss it.
Oh, and please click the "Good" button.
Please give us a "Good" button, too.
Let's end with a name.
Rina Matsuda and..,
Morinaga and,
Morinaga, and Misaki Ohno,
Yamashita Suzuki.
Bye bye! Sakura Saka Channel Bakubaku Bakubaku Bakubaku Bakubaku Bakubaku
Bakubaku Bakubaku Bakubaku
You, who are walking through life
Hurry up and go around!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Watch the Sakura Saka Channel!
There is an announcement!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
On May 4th, we're going to do a live broadcast on Sakura-saka channel!
I have a favor to ask you.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
We will be broadcasting in the winter and spring of peace, so please hurry up and hurry up and hurry up!
Power Mode If You Hurry
Hurry up and turn!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
UsWe
We have a dream
the more we hustle, the more we go
Faster or slower, faster or slower, faster or slower
Faster or slower, faster or slower, faster or slower, faster or slower, faster or slower, faster or slower
We want the whole of Japan to see it
I want the world to see it
And may the circle of Bajeez spread even wider!
Kaba kaba maware
I promise it will be a unique channel!
Kabaka bakaba wo maware
even if you don't know us, we'll make you feel like you've unearthed ammonite
we will make you feel like you've unearthed an ammonite even if you don't know us
Earth
3 days to go until the live broadcast Bye!